<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mangasf Project</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/</link><description>Recent content on Mangasf Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve the engagement on remote teams</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/improve-the-engagement-on-remote-teams/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/improve-the-engagement-on-remote-teams/</guid><description>Since the beginning of the 21st century, some companies in the sector have implemented work models in which employees can work from home one or more days a week. Some companies even ventured to implement it completely, in some cases without physical offices.
If we talk about companies with remote work models, we have to mention Basecamp. The American company specializing in the creation of project management software has never had a head office.</description></item><item><title>Note-taking with Notion and ChatGPT for effective meetings</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/note-taking-with-notion-and-chatgpt-for-effective-meetings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/note-taking-with-notion-and-chatgpt-for-effective-meetings/</guid><description>As an Engineering Manager, taking notes during meetings can be an essential tool to help you stay organized, stay on track, and ensure that you and your team are aligned and moving towards your goals.
Why take notes in your meetings? Here are some specific reasons why taking notes during meetings is important:
Record of Decisions and Action Items: By taking notes during meetings, you can capture important decisions, action items, and commitments made by both yourself and your team members.</description></item><item><title>Radical Candor: The Key to Building High-Performing Teams</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/radical-candor-the-key-to-building-high-performing-teams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/radical-candor-the-key-to-building-high-performing-teams/</guid><description>Creating high-performing teams is important for several reasons. First, high-performing teams are more productive and efficient, which can lead to increased profitability and competitiveness for the organization. Second, high-performing teams tend to be more innovative and adaptable, allowing the organization to respond more effectively to changes in the market and external environment.
As a leader, creating high-performing teams can also enhance your reputation and career prospects. When you are able to build and lead successful teams, you are more likely to be seen as a valuable asset to the organization, and you may be given more opportunities for advancement and leadership roles in the future.</description></item><item><title>How to Be an Effective Engineering Mentor: Tips and Strategies</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/how-to-be-an-effective-engineering-mentor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/how-to-be-an-effective-engineering-mentor/</guid><description>Mentoring is an important aspect of professional development for engineers. A good mentor can provide guidance, advice, and support to help their mentee grow and achieve their career goals. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in becoming a mentor, here are some tips to help you get started:
Set expectations early
When you first start mentoring an engineer, it&amp;rsquo;s important to set expectations early on. Discuss your role as a mentor and what you hope to achieve through the mentoring relationship.</description></item><item><title>Accelerate the development of your product through Outsourcing techniques</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/outsourcing-to-accelerate-product-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/outsourcing-to-accelerate-product-development/</guid><description>There are different moments in the development of a product in which market times or other factors make you cannot reach internally the speed of development that your business needs. On these occasions the Outsourcing or outsourcing the development of parts of your product can be an interesting solution to your problem.
Outsourcing in the world of software is the process by which a company chooses to outsource to a company external services related to the development of a technological product.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About us</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/about-us/</guid><description>The Mangasf Project was born with the intention of helping companies to solve their problems by building technological solutions. For this, the project relies on a group of professionals with extensive experience in the IT sector. This group of professionals is led by engineer Fran Mangas.
The essence of the service offered by the project is to provide a comprehensive consulting model. This service covers from the support for the construction of equipment to the accompaniment in the implementation of solutions.</description></item><item><title>About us</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/about-us/</guid><description>Computer Engineer specialized in computer science and web programming performance. I have studied at the UC (University of Cantabria) and at the Ramon Llull University of Barcelona.
I have been linked to the IT sector for the last 10 years, working in different types of industries. I have always held development and technical leadership roles from the early stages of biotech startups, from consulting to end product companies.
My career in the private sector has always been linked parallel to teaching and entrepreneurship.</description></item><item><title>1:1 meetings as a thermometer for changes in the team</title><link>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/meets-one-to-one/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mangasf-project.com/en/posts/meets-one-to-one/</guid><description>One of the challenges we have when we are working in management or team management is to measure the adaptation that these have to the various changes that we are applying. The second challenge we could say is to detect if before or after the application of certain changes there are points that affect the productivity of the group or any of its members. In order to be able to measure these points, we must have a tool that allows us to capture information and analyze it.</description></item></channel></rss>